Guide to the Annette Weiner Papers MC 152
New York University Archives
- Series VIII: Professional Organizations
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Cornman, Jack, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Goldschmidt, Walter, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Lee, Richard B., undated (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Morris, C. Pattrick, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Overbey, Peggy, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Schneider, David M., 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Swedlund, Alan, 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - AAA's - American Ethnologist Book Review Author, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - AAA's Task Force- AIDS Crisis Task force, 1989-1990 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - AAA's Task Force- Computer Task Force, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - AAA's Task Force- Environment Task Force, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - AAA's Task Force- President's Meeting, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - AAA's Task Force- President's Meeting and Summit Meeting, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - AAA's Task Force- Summary of AAA Task Force, Panels, and Commissions, undated (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - AAA's Task Force- Teaching Task Force, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - AAA's - Topic on 'Reproduction and Social Theory", 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - AAA's Reorganization, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - SCA Correspondence- Atkinson, Jane Monnig, 1987-1988 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8045 1
  - SCA Correspondence- D'Andrade, Roy G. (secretary), 1981-1987 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - SCA Correspondence- Hymes, Dell H., 1982 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - SCA Correspondence- Lavenda, Robert H., 1985 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - SCA Correspondence- Lehman, Edward J., 1982-1987 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - SCA Correspondence- Lieber, M., undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - SCA Correspondence- Marcus, George E., 1985-1987 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - SCA Correspondence- Schneider, David M.., 1982-1988 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - SCA Correspondence- Watson, James B., 1982 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - SCA Correspondence- Summary of SCA Discussions, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - SCA Correspondence- Constitution and By-Laws of the AAA, 1973, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - SCA Correspondence- Proposal Article of Incorporation of AAA, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - SCA Correspondence- Agenda Issues & Addresses of Correspondents, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - SCA- First Meeting of Society of Cultural Anthropology, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - SCA- Spring Meeting: Cultural Boarders, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - SCA-Program Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- Series IX: Students Dissertations and her dissertation
  This series contains the dissertations of Weiners advisees including Weiners dissertation
  - Fiorini, Marcelo Oppido: Construing Nambiquara Personhood through Naming Practices, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8046 9
  - Bohan, Nancy Ellen: The Sexes in the Value Systems of the Trobriand Islands and of the Dobu District, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Damon, Frederick Henry: Modes of Production and the Circulation of Value on the Other Side of the Kula Ring, Woodlark Island, Muyuw, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Hutchins, Edwin Lee, Jr.: Reasoning in Discourse: An Analysis of Trobriand Island Land Litigation, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Montague Susan: The Trobriand Society, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Norick, Frank Albert: An Analysis of the Material Culture of the Trobriand Islands, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8047 7
  - Renne, Elisha P.: Wives, Chiefs, and Weavers: Gender Relations in Bunu Yoruba Society, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Powell, H. A.: An Analysis of Present Day Social Structure in the Trobriand Islands Volume I, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8048 5
  - Powell, H. A.: An Analysis of Present Day Social Structure in the Trobriand Islands Volume II, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Sloan, William N.: Valuables and Vegetables: An Alliance Theory Investigation of Trobriand Society, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8049 3
  - Stoller, Paul Allen: The dynamics of Bankwano: Communication and Political Legitimacy among the Songhai (Republic of Naiger), 1978 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Theroux, Paul: Under the Spell of the Trobriand Islands, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Uberoi, J.P.Singh: Politics of the Kula Ring: An Analysis of the Findings of Bronislaw Malinowski, 1962, 1971 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Weiner, Anette B.: Women of Value: The Main Road of Exchange in Kiriwina, Trobriand Islands Part I, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Weiner, Annette B.: Women of Value: The Main Road of Exchange in Kiriwina, Trobriand Islands Part II, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Teckle, Belainesh; The Position of Women in Fiji: Vatulele, a Case Study Volume I, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8050 1
  - Teckle, Belainesh; The Position of Women in Fiji: Vatulele, a Case Study Volume II, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 2)